关于蝙蝠侠我有个问题
I have a question about Batman.
蝙蝠侠是个打扮像蝙蝠的人
Batman is a man who dresses up like a bat.
侠蝙蝠则是人和蝙蝠的混合体
Man-bat is a part man, part bat hybrid.
那么
Now,
如果侠蝙蝠打扮成人的样子抗击犯罪
if Man-Bat dressed up as a man to fight crime,
他该叫做侠蝙蝠侠吗?
would he be Man-Batman?
不 他该叫做蝙蝠侠蝙蝠
No, he'd be Bat-Man-Bat.
可侠蝙蝠侠不就是
But wouldn't Man-Batman just be a Batman
一个被受辐射的人类咬过的蝙蝠侠吗?
that was bitten by a radioactive man?
可蝙蝠侠是个人啊
But Batman is a man.
你说的是有正常人类能力的人
You're talking about a man who would have the powers of a man.
那就是人侠
That's just Man-Man.
人侠不就是普通的人吗?
Well, isn't Man-Man just Man?
可如果人侠打扮成蝙蝠的样子呢?
But what if Man-Man dressed as a bat?
那就是蝙蝠侠了
Well, that's just Batman.
不对 如果人打扮成蝙蝠的样子
No, if a man dresses as a bat,
就是蝙蝠侠 可如果人侠打扮成蝙蝠的样子
that's Batman, but if Man-Man dresses as a bat,
那就是蝙蝠人侠
that's Batman-Man.
这个回答满意吗?
So does that answer your question?
我还没问问题呢
Oh, I haven't asked it yet.
Claire发消息了 得走了
Oh, that's Claire. Got to run.
还以为你和Emily和好了
I thought you were back with Emily.
事实上我两边都见着...呢
Uh, actually I'm... seeing both of them.
你是说躲在窗外的林子里偷窥?
You mean like through their window from behind a bush?
不 事实上我同时和她们两个约会
No, I'm actually dating two women.
待会见
Later.
扯呢吧?
Really?
好几年都不能和女人说话的家伙
The guy who for years couldn't even talk to women
现在同时交往两个女人了?
is suddenly going out with two of them?
- 那怎么可能啊?  - 是啊
- How is that possible?  - I know.
科学家已经尝试过用
Scientists have tried to reproduce it
计算模型来重现它了
with computational models,
可是 在所有情况下 世界都会崩溃
but, in each case, the world blows up.
说真的 那个家伙现在同时和两个女人约会?
Seriously, that guy's dating two women?
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第九季第21集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 酥酥要变瘦 沫纸也要变瘦
校对: UUUUUU
翻译: 無限月讀  钥匙君
翻译: 李小宝Licht  肉肉君
你搞这些派对用的长面包干什么?
What, why did you get a party sub?
反正有人来 这东西看起来挺有意思的
People are coming over; it looked fun.
我们不过是要看权力的游戏而已
Well, we're only watching Game of Thrones.
派对面包说明这是一场派对
A party sub implies it's a party.
可你参加的话就不算是了
Your attendance implies it's not.
我和其他人喜欢派对的程度是一样的
I like a party as much as the next man,
只要其他人不那么喜欢开派对
as long as the next man doesn't like a party.
随便说一句 别忘了
Oh, by the way, don't forget,
明天是每季度的室友协议会谈
tomorrow is our quarterly Roommate Agreement meeting.
Sheldon 我们不需要每三个月
Oh, Sheldon, we don't need a meeting
就搞一次会谈 不是吗?
every three months. Hmm?
听起来很像是能在每季度的室友协议会谈上
Well, it sounds like the kind of thing one would bring up
提出的议题呢
at a quarterly Roommate Agreement meeting.
啊正好 就是明天了
Lucky for you it's tomorrow.
你知道吗?
Oh, you know what?
我不想参加
I'm not going.
你必须参加
Well, you have to go.
这是Penny第一次领头宣誓誓词
It's Penny's first time leading the Pledge of Allegiance.
会谈就是浪费时间
This meeting is a waste of time.
我们是否
Whether we make the switch
从Post牌的葡萄干麦片换成Kellogg牌的葡萄干麦片
from Post Raisin Bran to Kellogg's Raisin Bran
不需要走议会程序
should not require parliamentary procedure.
你知道他们之一有在葡萄干上放糖
You realize one of them has sugar on the raisins.
只有你一个人吃那些东西!
You're the only one who eats them!
然而你有发表意见的权力
And yet you get to weigh in.
这是民主... 很有意思 不是吗?
Democracy... it's pretty cool, isn't it?
我不参加 你不能逼我参加
I'm not going; you can't make me.
那我们走着瞧
Well, we'll just see about that.
怎么了?
What is the problem?
他说他不参加
He says he's not coming
明天的室友协议会谈
to the Roommate Agreement meeting tomorrow.
天啊 那我还背宣誓词干什么吗?
Well, why the hell did I memorize the Pledge?
你自娱自乐去吧 我不参加
You have fun. I will not be attending.
好吧 如果你不愿意的话
Oh, fine. We don't have to have
我们可以不搞室友协议会谈
a Roommate Agreement meeting if you don't want to.
- 多谢  - 当然了 这得投票决定
- Thank you.  - Of course, it will require a vote.
不幸的是 正式的法槌在我卧室里
Unfortunately, my official gavel is in my bedroom,
幸运的是 我还准备了便携法槌
but luckily, I have my travel gavel.
你在无理取闹
You're being ridiculous.
现在有一个提案 我在无理取闹
There's a motion on the floor, "I'm ridiculous."
有人支持吗?
Do we have a second?
没人支持
Hmm? Hmm? There is no second.
否决提案
The motion is denied.
下次 先确保有人投票支持你
Next time, make sure you have the votes first.
很难看呢
That was embarrassing.
你能跟他谈谈吗?
Can you please talk to him?
为啥你要在这事上跟他较劲?
Well, why are you fighting him on this?
因为我讨厌总是顺着他
Because I am tired of him always getting his way.
根本不需要开什么傻兮兮的会
We don't need a stupid meeting.
我们甚至不需要有室友协议
We don't even need a Roommate Agreement,
希望这面包真的能开得起派对就好了!
and I hope that sandwich does cause a party!
我还是会参加你的会谈的
Well, I will still come to your meeting.
但愿如此 明天还得照相呢
Well, I should hope so. Tomorrow's picture day.
为啥你要支持他?
Why are you taking his side?
因为对他来说很重要
Because it's important to him,
我们签署了室友协议 就算达成了一致
and when we signed the Roommate Agreement, we made a deal.
继续那么说 你就可以参加护旗队了
Y-You keep talking like that, you're gonna make color guard.
- 哥们 我累死了  - 我知道
- Man, I'm worn out.  - I know.
要是在真实世界里走这么久就更累了
Imagine if we were actually moving.
不是这个 只是 自从我开始跟Claire和Emily同时交往后
No, it's just, ever since I started dating Claire and Emily
我就感觉到精疲力尽
at the same time, it's exhausting.
你精疲力尽?
You're exhausted?
为了让你的老婆知道你在读育儿书
Try folding every five pages in a pregnancy book
然后每隔五页折一次书 这才叫累
so your wife thinks you read it.
但是你比我幸运的多啊
But, dude, you're so lucky.
晚上你还能和自己的爱人待在一起
Getting to stay home at night with the woman you love.
那我是比较幸运
I guess I am lucky.
就是啊 因为同时撩两个妹子
You are, because dating two women,
我甚至都不记得
I mean, I can't even remember
上一次在自己家睡觉是什么时候的事了
the last time I slept in my own apartment.
每次我醒来就在想"我在Claire家还是在Emily家
I wake up and I'm like, "Am I at Claire's or am I at Emily's?
或者是在第三个我忘记是谁的女孩子家?"
Is there a third girl I've forgotten about?"
就像是...
Like...
"我到底在哪儿?"
"Where am I?"
嗨Raj
Hey, Raj.
嘿 准妈妈做得怎么样了?
Hey, how's the mommy-to-be?
还好啦 就是有点累
Good. A little tired.
我理解你 我现在正脚踏几只船呢
I feel you. I've been dating multiple women.
你确定你真的不想
You sure you don't want to come
和我们一起看权力的游戏?
watch Game of Thrones with us?
你们玩吧
You guys have fun.
我就想躺在床上看会儿书
I'm just gonna snuggle up in bed with a book.
这太好了... 睡自己的床
Oh, that sounds great... a bed to yourself.
我已经不知道这是什么感觉了
Can't even remember what that's like.
你一直在追权力的游戏吗?
Are you up-to-date on Game of Thrones?
可能吧
Mm, I think so.
就是龙啊 冰雪僵尸啊 还有所有的帅小伙都死了
Dragons, snow zombies, and all the hot guys are dead.
这我就不清楚了
Oh, I don't know.
席恩·葛雷乔伊看着挺不错的
Theon Greyjoy looks pretty good
对于一个小丁丁被割掉的人来说
for a guy who had his genitals cut off.
有个小朋友还在生气呢
Uh-oh, somebody's still pouting.
别管我
Leave me alone.
如果是因为你弄丢了你的丁丁
If it's because you lost a stick,
我知道它去哪儿了
I know where it went.
一点也不好笑
Not funny.
你知道你最终会和他重归于好的
You know you're gonna make up with him.
那我们直接跳到最后一步不行吗?
Can we just skip to that part?
当然了 因为我是这里唯一的成年人嘛
Oh, of course, because I'm the only adult around here.
真的吗? 唯一的成年人?
Really? The only adult?
是的 就是这样
Yeah, that's right.
今晚我要看的剧是M.A.限制级的
Tonight I'll be watching a show rated M.A.,
专门给"成熟的观众"看的 小鬼
and that stands for "Mature Audiences," buster.
好了 你应该明白作为"唯一的成年人"
All right, you would think "the only adult"
是不会让这点小事毁了真个晚上的
wouldn't let something silly ruin our entire night.
我觉得你应该明白为什么我这么生气
And I'd think you'd understand why I'm annoyed.
只要你去参加会议这些都可以被避免啊
All this could be avoided if you'd just come to the meeting.
我就是不想去
I don't want to.
这就是个会而已
Oh, it's just a meeting.
- 就一个简单的小会  - 不要再说"开会"了!
- One simple meeting.  - Stop saying "meeting"!
# 开会 开会 就开会 #
# Meeting, meeting, bo-beeting #
# 今天开会 明天开会 #
# Banana-fana, fo-feeting #
# 就是一直要开会... #
# Fee-fi mo-meeting... #
我带了我最拿手的菠菜酱
I brought my famous spinach dip.
嘿Amy 等一会
Yo, Amy, just one second.
# 开会 #
# Meeting. #
我不知道我想要男孩还是女孩
I'm not sure if I'm hoping for a boy or a girl.
如果是男孩
I mean, if it's a boy,
我就得教他怎么接球
I'm gonna have to teach him to play catch.
也就是说我得自己谷歌搜索
Which means I'm gonna have to Google
"怎么接球"
"How to play catch."
如果是女孩...
If it's a girl, I mean...
女孩太无辜脆弱了... 你知道男的都是什么鸟样
they're so innocent and... you know how guys are.
就是 男人真是太坏了
Totally, guys are the worst.
我想说 看看哥
I mean, look at me.
我让Emily给我做了煎饼果子
I let Emily make me a frittata
那晚我把吃剩下的放到了Claire的冰箱里
and I kept the leftovers in Claire's fridge that night.
我真是一个坏男孩
I'm such a dog.
又来了
There you go again.
对不起 我是不是抱怨太多了?
I'm sorry, have I been complaining about it too much?
你只是一直在假装抱怨
Actually, what you're doing is pretending to complain,
实际上你一直在炫耀
but really trying to brag.
你为什么这么说?
How could you say that?
"我多想在没有女生和我做羞羞事的时候
"Oh, I wish could enjoy a cup of tea
就简简单单喝一杯茶"
without a naked girl bouncing up and down on me."
我从没说过这个啊
I never said that.
"当你在沙发缝里找到其他女人的内衣
"Don't you hate it when you can't remember whose bra it is
但是不知道是谁的时候 简直抓狂啊"
you found wedged in your couch?"
好吧 这我的确说过
Okay, that I said.
但是这真是我的苦恼啊!
But that's a real problem!
你要是给错别人的内衣了
You give a girl another woman's bra,
那晚你就别想和她做羞羞的事了
and you will not be having sex with her that night.
或许可以和另外一个她做 但不是这个她
Maybe the other girl, but not her.
他怎么了?
What's going on with him?
他正为室友协定会议
Oh, he's all bent out of shape
生气着呢
about having a Roommate Agreement meeting.
看起来 全勤奖已经对他没有吸引力了
Apparently, perfect attendance isn't cool anymore.
不用担心 他会好的
Don't worry, he'll come around.
我理解他为什么这么生气
Well, I get why he's annoyed.
那是你不知道发生了什么
Well, then you don't understand what's happening.
你看...
See...
Leonard拒绝参加
Leonard refused to participate
每季强制性的室友协定会议
in a mandatory quarterly Roommate Agreement meeting.
这就是看巴特·辛普森长大的人的样子
This is what a generation raised on Bart Simpson looks like.
你不就喜爱辛普森一家
You love The Simpsons.
我喜欢的是丽萨·辛普森
I love Lisa Simpson.
我知道他的感受
Well, I know how he feels.
我也从不喜欢我们的恋爱关系协定会议
I never enjoyed our Relationship Agreement meetings.
等会儿
Wait.
你是装作喜欢的吗?
You were pretending?
对不起
Sorry.
不是吧!
No!
我才不信呢 我看得出来你很享受
I don't believe you. I could tell.
噢 Sheldon
"Oh, Sheldon,
我从没想过
"I never thought
聚在一起
"re-filing a matter
重新审核事宜是一件这么有意思的事
in a standing subcommittee could be so fascinating."
这个嘛 你怎么看?
Hmm, what do you think?
你不会看不出来吧?
You don't know?
嘿 我说了什么让你不爽的话吗?
Hey, did I say something to upset you?
没有 我很好
No, I'm fine.
真的吗? 可是你平常都是和人家肩并肩一起走的
Really? Because usually we walk side by side,
但现在整整爬了两层楼
and I just went up two flights of stairs
我只能一直盯着你的屁股
staring at your bottom.
别放在心上
Just drop it.
好吧 我知道是怎么回事了
Okay, I think I see what's happening here.
你嫉妒我了
You're jealous of me.
拜托
Oh, please.
你有什么让我好嫉妒的?
What could you possibly have that I would be jealous of?
不是我有什么 而是有几个人和我一起做什么
It's not what I have, it's how many people I'm having it with.
走吧 Sheldon 我们去我那里看权力的游戏
Come on, Sheldon, we'll watch Game of Thrones over here.
- 乐意之至  - 很好 走吧
- Gladly.  - Oh, good, go.
你知道 如果能
You know, it'll be nice
看完一整集都没有人一直啰嗦
to watch an episode without someone saying,
我看过书了
"I read the books.
别对这个角色付出太多感情
Don't get too fond of this character."
这不代表他们最后翘辫子了
It's not always because they die.
举个例子 是因为这些角色在凛冬将至时
In one case, it's because they've become involved
就和地底的森林之子产生了联系
with underground tree people from the dawn of time.
哼 就不告诉你是谁
Yeah, but I won't say who it is.
没错 就是Bran!
It's Bran!
这是怎么了?
Wait, what is going on?
Leonard是个混蛋 所以我们决定去这边看
Leonard's being a jerk, so we're gonna watch over here,
你们要和我们一起吗?
Do you guys want to watch with us?
只要不和这货一起看就行
As long as I don't have to watch with him.
很好 我也不想和你一起看
Fine, I don't want to watch with you either.
我去那边了
I'll go over here.
谁说你可以先选了?
Why do you get to pick?
行啊 那你过去!
Okay, then you go there!
我去哪边还用不着你指手画脚!
Don't tell me where to go!
Howard 进来吧
Howard, just come in here.
来这边 Raj
Yeah, come on, Raj.
等一下 Amy做了她拿手的菠菜酱了吗?
Wait, did Amy make her spinach dip?
她做了
She did.
我连渣儿都不会给你剩!
And I'm gonna eat it all!
到底是什么情况啊?
So what the hell happened?
只不过是我实在没耐心去应付Sheldon的无理取闹罢了
Oh, I just ran out of patience with Sheldon's nonsense.
深有体会 我也受不了Raj了
Tell me about it. I've had it with Raj, too.
就像女人一样 男人每个月也总有那么几天
You know, like women, men have a monthly hormone cycle.
睾丸素的分泌下降会导致情绪反复无常
Dips in testosterone can cause irritability.
有意思
Interesting.
说不定我的男性周期和Raj的大姨妈同步了呢
Maybe my male cycle synced up with Raj's actual period.
如果Sheldon的睾丸素分泌再下降 他就上天了
If Sheldon's testosterone dipped, he'd become a butterfly.
瞧瞧
Oh.
看来是有人知道自己错了呢
Maybe someone's here to apologize.
嘿 Leonard
Hey, Leonard.
Stuart你好
Stuart.
额...
Uh...
这不是化妆派对啊?
Is this not a dress-up party?
不是
No.
本来也不是的哈?
Was it ever a dress-up party?
不是
No.
Howard 你不是告诉我这是化妆派对吗?
Howard, didn't you tell me it was a dress-up party?
我是这么说的
Yeah.
他们说如果不爽Howard就到这里来
I was told this is where to go if I'm mad at Howard.
你要脱掉你的斗篷吗?
May I take your cloak?
谢谢
Thanks.
这玩意儿一直铰在我自行车的链条里
This thing kept getting caught in the chain of my bike.
我给你补充下背景知识
Well, I'll catch you up.
Penny不爽Leonard Leonard不爽我和Penny
Uh, Penny is angry at Leonard, Leonard's angry at me and Penny,
我对Leonard和Amy不爽
I'm angry at Leonard and Amy,
Raj对Howard不爽
Raj is angry at Howard,
我还很不爽George R.R. Martin
and I'm angry at George R.R. Martin
因为他没有新书可以让我剧透给Leonard
'cause there are no new books for me to spoil for Leonard.
你和Howard之间怎么了?
So what happened with you and Howard?
他说我一直说和Claire和
Says I was talking too much
Emily同时约会的事情
about dating Claire and Emily,
我还说他是在嫉妒我
and I accused him of being jealous.
人家很眼红啊
I'm jealous.
最接近我和两个女人同时约会的时候
Closest I've come to dating two women
就是我和一个女人约会的时候
was that time I dated one woman.
我不知道你怎么受得了
I don't know how you put up with it.
他简直不可理喻 想想看 就连决定
He's impossible. I mean, holding a meeting
我们究竟要买哪种早餐麦片都要开会
to decide what breakfast cereal we should buy.
就是说 当然是Cap'n Crunch和Crunch Berries 下一项
Yeah. Cap'n Crunch with Crunch Berries, move on.
无论怎样 Amy 谢谢你站在我这边
Anyway, Amy, thank you for sticking up for me.
说实在的 姐一点都不在乎
Oh, I honestly couldn't care less.
啥?
Sorry?
我站在你这边纯粹是因为我对Sheldon和Penny
Well, I just took your side 'cause sometimes I get annoyed
走得太近而不爽
at how close Sheldon and Penny are.
他们一直吵来吵去的
Well, they argue all the time.
也没那么亲近啦
They aren't that close.
那他失落的时候是谁一直在安慰他?
Who's always comforting him when he's upset?
是Penny没错 但... 那又只有谁
Penny, but... Who's the only one
可以让他在生病的时候乖乖吃药?
who can make him take his medicine when he's sick?
我试过把药藏在他的花生酱里
I try to hide it in his peanut butter,
但他吐出来了
but he spits it out.
好嘛
Okay.
你知道Penny让Sheldon
And did you know she has him add things
往室友条例里加条款 这样她就能想干嘛干嘛
to the Roommate Agreement so she can get her way
而不用和你争辩吗?
and not fight with you about it?
这个混蛋
Son of a bitch.
这有啥好笑的?
Why is that funny?
我也不知道 我喜欢看着别人受苦
I don't know. I like the pain of others.
那好 你应该会喜欢这个
Oh, well, then you'll enjoy this.
Bernadette对你和Koothrappali做了同样的事
Bernadette does the same thing with you and Koothrappali.
才没有
No, she doesn't.
她一直为他辩护
She defends him all the time.
才不是
She does not.
是谁告诉你
Who told you to stop making
不要对他讲各种甘地笑话的?
all those Gandhi jokes about him?
这确实是她说的
Well, she did.
人力资源部也和我说过
And human resources.
你觉得是谁告诉Koothrappali
Who do you think told Koothrappali
去找人力资源部的?
to go to human resources?
这个混蛋
Son of a bitch.
你太对了 感觉真好
You're right, it feels good.
嗯 游戏时间到了
All right, it's almost game time.
懂了吗?
Get it?
权利的游戏 游戏时间?
Game of Thrones, game time?
两个女人 是吧?
Two women, huh?
看来Amy是想明白了
Oh, perhaps it's Amy coming to her senses.
- 怎么了?  - 你知道
- What's up?  - You know,
你不需要通过Sheldon那傻瓜室友条例
you don't need to use Sheldon to get your way with me
来绕过我吧?
in a dumb Roommate Agreement.
你从哪知道的?
Where'd you get that from?
Amy说的
From Amy.
呃 Amy 你为啥告诉他这个?
Ugh. Amy, why did you tell him that?
因为你和往常一样袒护Sheldon
Because you were defending Sheldon like you always do.
我平常才不袒护Sheldon呢
I don't always defend Sheldon.
你当然袒护他 你知道你和他有种奇怪的
Oh, yes, you do. You know you have a weird
梗来自电影E.T外星人 本片中男主和他的兄妹们联手帮外星人找回了家
兄妹外星关系
brother-sister-Elliott-E.T. relationship with him.
那你和他奇怪的关系呢?
What about your weird relationship with him?
这是另一码事
That's different.
我是鬼驱人里面那个小女孩
I'm like the little girl in Poltergeist
他是电视里那个可怕的东西
and he's the creepy thing in the TV.
各位
Um, guys?
食物里面有坚果吗?
Were there any nuts in that food?
- 应该没有吧 怎么了?  - 嗯...
- I don't think so. Why?  - Well...
只是感觉不大对头
Just a feeling.
上面只写着"意大利三明治"
It just said "Italian sub."
我完全不知道摩泰台拉香肚(一种熏香肠)里面有开心果
I had no idea mortadella has pistachios in it.
小知识:
Interesting fact:
在意大利语里 "摩泰台拉香肚"里的"摩泰"意思是死亡
In Italian, the "morta" in "mortadella" means death.
Sheldon啊
Sheldon.
我又没说"趣味小知识" 我不是怪物
I didn't say "fun" fact. I'm not a monster.
他会没事的
He's gonna be okay.
现在就是趣味小知识了
Now it's a fun fact.
天啊 这种事情发生真的让你好好思考人生啊
Boy, stuff like this really puts things in perspective.
你为啥穿成这样?
Why are you dressed like that?
呃 Howard觉得告诉我这是化妆派对
Oh, uh, Howard thought it'd be funny
是件有趣的事
to tell me it was a costume party.
这可不好
That wasn't nice.
确实 不过他都快死了 我俩两清了吧
No, but he almost died, so we're cool.
其实 你仔细想想 今晚就像是
You know, if you think about it, tonight was kind of like
现实版的权利的游戏
a real-life Game of Thrones.
怎么像?
How?
Howard吃了开心果
Well, Howard eating that pistachio
就像乔佛瑞国王被毒死了
was like when King Joffrey got poisoned.
那是谋杀 这是意外
Okay, well, that was murder, this was an accident.
好吧
Okay.
但你利用Sheldon
But you using Sheldon
暗箱操作就像瑟曦
to do your dirty work is like when Cersei
利用国王的守卫来垂帘听政一样
used the King's Guard to do her bidding.
瑟曦用肉体操纵别人
Cersei uses her body to manipulate men.
Penny只是带我去了乐高玩具店
Penny just takes me to The LEGO Store.
那这样呢?
Okay. Oh, how about this?
Stuart穿得就像守夜人军团
Stuart's dressed like a brother of the Night's Watch,
而且他们不啪啪啪
and they don't have sex.
- 说到点子上了  - 没错
- There you go.  - That's true.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 你还好吗?
Hey. You all right?
我很好
I'm fine.
就是觉得被当个婴儿从楼梯上抬下来
Just a little embarrassed I had to be carried down the stairs
有些尴尬
like a baby.
谢谢
Thanks.
我们走吧
Let's get out of here.
太吓人了
That was scary.
重要的是
Well, the important thing is
我之前就说这个大三明治会毁了一切的
I said that big sandwich would ruin everything,
我说对了
and I was right.
嘿 琼恩·雪诺!
Hey, Jon Snow!
你的马上为啥有个筐子?
How come your horse has a basket on it?
你的头上怎么有一张脸?
How come your head has your face on it?
权力的游戏里他们不戴自行车头盔
They don't wear bicycle helmets in Game of Thrones.
你的主题不对
You're thematically inaccurate,
但我为你的安全意识鼓掌
but I applaud your commitment to safety.
你们就没些更好的事做吗?
Don't you guys have anything better to do?
比看一个穿着毛皮斗篷的男人
Better than watching a guy in a fur cloak
骑一辆女自行车还好的? 没有了
ride a girl's bike?  Nope.
就这样了 你才失去了你在漫画店的
That's it, you just lost bathroom privileges
厕所特权
at the comic book store.
有筐子的马 真蠢...
Horse has a basket on it. Stupid...
Leonard啊
Leonard.
Leonard Leonard啊
Leonard. Leonard.
什么事?
What?
我那关于蝙蝠侠的问题还没问呢
I never got to ask my question about Batman.
啥问题?
What is it?
如果蝙蝠侠被一个放射性侠蝙蝠咬了
If Batman were bitten by a radioactive Man-Bat,
并假扮侠蝙蝠和罪犯斗争
and then fought crime disguised as Man-Bat,
是应该叫他人形侠蝙蝠蝙蝠侠
would he be Man-Bat-Man-Bat-Man
还是只是侠蝙蝠人形蝙蝠侠就好?
or simply Man-Bat-Man-Bat-Batman?
他侠蝙蝠衣服里面有蝙蝠侠衣服吗?
Is he still wearing the Batman suit under the Man-Bat suit?
我马上回来
I'll be back.